How far would you go to win the ultimate job?
Exam is a thriller, mystery film directed by Stuart Hazeldine.
Eight talented candidates have reached the final stage of selection to
join the ranks of a mysterious and powerful corporation.
Entering a windowless room, where an armed guard keeps watch, they
are given 80 minutes to answer one simple question.
White, played by Luke Mably.
Black, played by Chukwudi Iwuji.
Dark, played by Adar Beck.
Brown, played by Jimi Mistry.
Blonde, played by Nathalie Cox.
Brunette, played by Pollyanna McIntosh.
Exam is a 2009 British psychological thriller film produced, written and directed by Stuart Hazeldine and starring Colin Salmon, Chris Carey,
Jimi Mistry, Luke Mably, Gemma Chan, Chukwudi Iwuji, John Lloyd Fillingham, Pollyanna McIntosh, Adar Beck and Nathalie Cox.
In the film, eight candidates for a highly desirable corporate job are locked together in
an exam room and given a final test with one seemingly simple question.
However, confusion soon ensues and tensions unravel.
The film explores themes of gun, riddle, room, guard, suspicion.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.